<Product Revision="2" xmlns="https://github.com/OpenZWave/open-zwave">
  <MetaData>
    <MetaDataItem name="OzwInfoPage">http://www.openzwave.com/device-database/015D:241C:0112</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductPic">images/zooz/zen22.png</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="241C" name="ZWProductPage" type="0112">https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/1946/</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ResetDescription">The switch will be reset to factory defaults only by exclusion using a Z-Wave controller. You may use any certified Z-Wave controller to exclude and reset the switch. This device may not be reset manually when the network’s primary controller is missing or otherwise inoperable. NOTE: All previously recorded activity and custom settings will be erased from the device’s memory.</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="Description">PRODUCT FEATURES:
- Manual or remote on/off control and dimming from your mobile device or computer (when included to a Z-Wave gateway controller)
- Z-Wave Plus with improved 500 chip for faster and safer wireless communication
- Works with most high-quality DIMMABLE LED, CFL, and incandescent bulbs
- Based on universal command classes - supported by most Z-Wave controllers
- May be associated and grouped with other Z-Wave devices for advanced home automation
- LED indicator to help locate the switch in dark space
- Simple elegant design with screwless snap-on wall plate included
- Built-in Z-Wave signal repeater for a stronger and more reliable network

SPECIFICATIONS:
Model Number: ZEN22
Z-Wave Signal Frequency: 908.42 MHz
Power: 120 VAC, 60 Hz
Maximum Loads: 500W Single-gang, 400W Double-gang, 300W Triple-gang Incandescent, 150W CFL or LED
Range: Up to 100 feet line of sight
Operating Temperature: 32-104° F (0-40° C)
Installation and Use: Indoor only</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductManual">https://Products.Z-WaveAlliance.org/ProductManual/File?folder=&amp;filename=Manuals/1946/zooz-z-wave-plus-dimmer-switch-zen22-manual.pdf</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="241C" name="FrequencyName" type="0112">U.S. / Canada / Mexico</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ExclusionDescription">1. Bring your Z-Wave gateway hub or controller as close to the switch as possible
2. Put your Z-Wave controller in exclusion mode
3. Tap the switch on and off quickly 3 times to complete the exclusion process
4. The device should disappear from your controller's device list</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="241C" name="Identifier" type="0112">ZEN22</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="Name">Zooz Z-Wave Dimmer Light Switch</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="InclusionDescription">1. Bring your Z-Wave gateway hub or controller as close to the switch as possible
2. Put your Z-Wave controller in inclusion mode
3. Tap the switch on and off quickly 3 times to finalize the inclusion process
4. A new dimming device should appear on your controller's device list

Troubleshooting Tips:
If you are unable to include the Z-Wave dimmer to your controller, please try one of the following:
- Bring the controller closer to your Z-Wave switch or use a hand-held secondary controller for inclusion
- Tap your Z-Wave switch quicker 4 or 5 times once you put the controller in the inclusion mode to ensure the command has gone through
- Put your controller in the EXCLUSION mode and tap the switch quickly 3 times, then try adding it to your network again</MetaDataItem>
    <ChangeLog>
      <Entry author="Justin Hammond - Justin@dynam.ac" date="24 May 2019" revision="2">Initial Metadata Import from Z-Wave Alliance Database - https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/1946/xml</Entry>
    </ChangeLog>
  </MetaData>
  <!-- https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/1946 -->
  <!-- Association Groups -->
  <CommandClass id="133">
    <Associations num_groups="1">
      <Group index="1" label="Lifeline" max_associations="5"/>
    </Associations>
  </CommandClass>
</Product>
