<Product Revision="2" xmlns="https://github.com/OpenZWave/open-zwave">
  <MetaData>
    <MetaDataItem name="OzwInfoPage">http://www.openzwave.com/device-database/027A:0005:0001</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductPic">images/zooz/zse29.png</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="0005" name="ZWProductPage" type="0001">https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/3081/</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="Description">FEATURES:
- Quick and reliable motion alerts to Z-Wave hub
- Outdoor ready housing (avoid direct sun and rain)
- Set motion time-out and lux trigger at the sensor
- Auto-inclusion for easy set-up
- The latest S2 security and Z-Wave Plus chip
- Powered by common batteries or Micro USB
- Built-in tamper switch for extra security

SPECS:
- Model Number: ZSE29
- Z-Wave Signal Frequency: 908.42 MHz
- Power: 3 x AA (1.5 V) batteries / Micro USB
- Motion Detection: up to 30 feet
- Operating Temperature: -4 – 104 F
- Warm-up time: 1 minute
- Range: Up to 130 feet line of sight
- Installation and Use: Indoor / Outdoor</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductManual">https://Products.Z-WaveAlliance.org/ProductManual/File?folder=&amp;filename=Manuals/3081/zooz-z-wave-plus-s2-outdoor-motion-sensor-zse29-manual.pdf</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="WakeupDescription">The sensor’s wake-up interval is set to 4 hours by default to save battery life. Use the Wake Up Command Class to adjust the interval (in seconds, working in 600s intervals, with 600 as min and 86400 as max values).
During wake-up, the sensor turns the Z-Wave radio on for 10 seconds to receive communication from the hub. Long wake-up interval will not affect how often the sensor reports motion to your hub.</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="Name">Outdoor Motion Sensor</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="0005" name="FrequencyName" type="0001">U.S. / Canada / Mexico</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ExclusionDescription">1. Bring the sensor within direct range of your Z-Wave
gateway (hub).
2. Put the Z-Wave hub into exclusion mode (not sure
how to do that? ask@getzooz.com).
3. Press and release the tamper switch 3 times quickly.
4. Your hub will confirm exclusion and the sensor will
disappear from your controller's device list.</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="InclusionDescription">AUTO-INCLUSION:
1. Initiate inclusion (pairing) in the app (or web interface). Not Sure how? ask@getzooz.com. If you’re using an S2 hub, it may ask you to enter the DSK key printed on the back cover sticker to complete secure inclusion.
2. Insert the batteries or the USB adapter board. The LED indicator
will start blinking and the sensor will join the network Automatically.

MANUAL INCLUSION:
Put your Z-Wave hub into inclusion mode and click the tamper switch 3 times quickly.</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ResetDescription">When your network’s primary controller is missing or otherwise inoperable, you may need to reset the device to factory settings manually. In order to complete the process, make sure the sensor is powered, then CLICKCLICK-CLICK-CLICK’N’HOLD the tamper switch for AT LEAST 5 SECONDS. The LED indicator will turn off to
indicate successful reset. The sensor will then enter auto-inclusion mode for 4 minutes.
NOTE: All previously recorded activity and custom settings will be erased from the device’s memory. </MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="0005" name="Identifier" type="0001">ZSE29</MetaDataItem>
    <ChangeLog>
      <Entry author="Justin Hammond - Justin@dynam.ac" date="03 Jun 2019" revision="2">Initial Metadata Import from Z-Wave Alliance Database - https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/3081/xml</Entry>
    </ChangeLog>
  </MetaData>
  <!-- Zooz ZSE29 Outdoor Motion Sensor -->

    <!-- Association Groups -->
  <CommandClass id="133">
    <Associations num_groups="2">
      <Group index="1" label="Lifeline" max_associations="1"/>
      <Group index="2" label="PIR Control" max_associations="4"/>
    </Associations>
  </CommandClass>
</Product>
