<?xml version='1.0'?>
<Product Revision="1" xmlns="https://github.com/OpenZWave/open-zwave">
   <!-- Please refer to https://github.com/OpenZWave/open-zwave/wiki/Adding-Devices for instructions -->
   <MetaData>
      <MetaDataItem name="Name">Namron Z-Wave 4 Channel Wall Remote K8</MetaDataItem>
      <MetaDataItem name="Description">The remote control is a Z-Wave device that can both control other Z-Wave devices and activate scenes in
         Gateways. Although it is controlling other devices, the device cannot act as Z-Wave network controller (primary
         or secondary) and will always need a Z-Wave network controller to be included into a Z-Wave network. It also
         supports the Over The Air (OTA) feature for the product’s firmware upgrade.

         The remote control has following functions:
         1. Control of groups of other Z-Wave devices using 'ON', 'OFF' and Dim commands.
         2. Activation of scenes in Gateway mode.

         The encryption modes that the remote control supports are S0, S2 Authenticated, S2 Unauthenticated. When
         the remote control is being included into a Z-Wave network, you can use your primary controller/gateway to
         enable one encryption mode or disable encryption. (The primary controller/gateway shall support
         encryption mode configuration).
      </MetaDataItem>
      <MetaDataItem name="OzwInfoPage">XX http://www.openzwave.com/device-database/0438:a305:0300</MetaDataItem>
      <MetaDataItem name="ProductPage">https://www.namron.com/products/namron-z-wave-4-kanaler-bryter-k8-854/</MetaDataItem>
      <MetaDataItem name="ProductSupport">https://www.namron.com/contact/</MetaDataItem>
      <MetaDataItem name="ProductPic">images/namron/4512714.jpg</MetaDataItem>
      <MetaDataItem name="ProductManual">https://www.elektroimportoren.no/docs/lib/4512714-Brukerveiledning-5.pdf</MetaDataItem>
      <MetaDataItem name="WakeupDescription">The remote control is under sleepy mode for most of the time to save battery power. It can not receive wireless
         command under sleepy mode. Before the gateway interacts data with the remote, the remote control shall be
         activated manually first. Short press any button to activate the remote control for 3s, and press and hold down
         I and O buttons of Group 2 over 1 second to activate the remote control</MetaDataItem>
      <MetaDataItem name="InclusionDescription">Step 1. Make sure the remote control does not belong to any Z-Wave network, short press any button, if LED 
         indicator does not turn on, the remote control does not belong to any network, then continue step 2,if LED indicator turns on, it means the remote
         control has already been included to a network, please first set the remote control to exclusion mode (refer to the part Exclusion"" of this manual),
         then continue step 2.
         
         Step 2. Set primary controller/gateway into inclusion mode (Please refer to your primary controllers manual on how to turn your controller into inclusion).
         
         Step 3. Press and hold down both buttons I and O of Group 2 over 3 seconds, LED indicator turns on, the remote control will be set to inclusion mode, 
         and waiting to be included, after 10s LED indicator blinks 6 times quickly to indicate successful inclusion. The remote control is a sleepy device, 
         after inclusion it will not enter into sleepy mode immediately, and will continue activation status for 30s and wait data interaction from the gateway, 
         the LED indicator will stay solid on, please be patient to wait LED indicator to turn off.
      </MetaDataItem>
      <MetaDataItem name="ExclusionDescription">There are two exclusion methods:
         Method 1: Exclusion from the primary controller/gateway as follows:
            1. Set the primary controller/gateway into exclusion mode (Please refer to your primary controllers manual on how to set your controller into exclusion).
            2. Press and hold down both buttons I and O of Group 2 over 3 seconds, LED indicator turns on, the remote control will be set to exclusion mode, and
            waiting to be excluded, after 7s LED indicator blinks 4 times quickly to indicate successful exclusion.
         Method 2: Factory reset the remote control will force the remote control to be excluded from a network. (please refer to the part “Factory Reset” of this manual)
      </MetaDataItem>
      <MetaDataItem name="ResetDescription">Press and hold down both buttons I and O of Group 2 for over 10 seconds, LED indicator turns on and then
         blinks 4 times quickly to indicate successful factory reset.Please use this procedure only when the network
         primary controller is missing or otherwise inoperable.</MetaDataItem>
      <MetaDataItem id="0xa305" name="ZWProductPage" type="0x0300">https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/3639</MetaDataItem>
      <MetaDataItem id="0xa305" name="FrequencyName" type="0x0300">CEPT</MetaDataItem>
      <MetaDataItem id="0xa305" name="Identifier" type="0x0300">4512720</MetaDataItem>
      <ChangeLog>
         <Entry author="Petter L. H. Eide" date="28 November 2020" revision="1">Initial addition of product definition.</Entry>
      </ChangeLog>
   </MetaData>
  <CommandClass id="112">
    <!-- Here is a Byte/Int/Short Value Sample -->
    <Value genre="config" index="1" label="Factory reset" max="21930" min="21930" type="int" units="" value="0" write_only="true">
      <Help>Set to 21930 to factory reset the device.</Help>
    </Value>
  </CommandClass>
  <CommandClass id="142">
    <Compatibility>
      <ForceInstances>true</ForceInstances>
    </Compatibility>
  </CommandClass>
  <CommandClass id="96">
    <Compatibility>
      <MapRootToEndpoint>true</MapRootToEndpoint>
    </Compatibility>
  </CommandClass>
   <!-- Association Groups -->
   <CommandClass id="133">
      <Associations num_groups="5">
         <Group index="1" label="Lifeline" max_associations="1" />
         <Group index="2" label="Button 1" max_associations="5" />
         <Group index="3" label="Button 2" max_associations="5" />
         <Group index="4" label="Button 3" max_associations="5" />
         <Group index="5" label="Button 4" max_associations="5" />
      </Associations>
   </CommandClass>
</Product>
