<Product Revision="5" xmlns="https://github.com/OpenZWave/open-zwave">
  <MetaData>
    <MetaDataItem name="OzwInfoPage">http://www.openzwave.com/device-database/000C:3034:4447</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductPic">images/homeseer/hs-wd100plus.png</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="3034" name="ZWProductPage" type="4447">https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/1731/</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ResetDescription">Please use this procedure only in the event that the network primary controller is lost or otherwise inoperable.

All Configuration Parameters can all be restored to their factory
default settings by using your primary controller to delete/reset
the device.   To manually reset, tap the ON button twice quickly and then tap the OFF button twice quickly.  Repeat the procedure to restore the settings to the factory default.
</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="Name">HS-WS100+ Wall Switch</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="3034" name="FrequencyName" type="4447">U.S. / Canada / Mexico</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="Description">HS-WS100+ In Wall On/Off Switch
• Supports wireless on-off control of lighting and appliance loads
• Z-Wave Plus certified for easy inclusion and reliable communications
• Compatible with HomeSeer (and many other) home controllers
• Includes double-tap, triple-tap, press &amp; hold event features to trigger up to 6 different home automation events
• Supports Z-Wave central scene technology
• Supports instant status when controlled locally
• Easy 'screw terminal' installation</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="InclusionDescription">1. Turn the connected appliance ON/OFF by tapping the switch. Tapping and releasing the upper part of the rocker turns the appliance ON. Tapping and releasing the lower part of the rocker turns the appliance OFF.
2. Add(Include) the module to/from your Z-Wave network with your primary controller. Please refer to the instructions manual of your gateway or remote controller for details and procedures on how these actions can be done. 
3. Normally, the sequence is as follows: when the inclusion process is prompted by your primary controller, single click and release the rocker switch to ON or OFF position.  The controller should show that the action was successful.  If the controller shows it was a fail, repeat the procedure.</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="3034" name="Identifier" type="4447">HS-WS100+</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductManual">https://Products.Z-WaveAlliance.org/ProductManual/File?folder=&amp;filename=Manuals/1731/HS-WS100-Manual-v1_1a.pdf</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ExclusionDescription">1. Turn the connected appliance ON/OFF by tapping the switch. Tapping and releasing the upper part of the rocker turns the appliance ON. Tapping and releasing the lower part of the rocker turns the appliance OFF.
2. Delete(Exclude) the module to/from your Z-Wave network with your primary controller. Please refer to the instructions manual of your gateway or remote controller for details and procedures on how these actions can be done. Normally, the sequence is as follows: when the exclusion process is prompted by your primary controller, single click and release the rocker switch.  The controller should show that the action was successful. If the controller shows it was a fail, repeat the procedure.</MetaDataItem>
    <ChangeLog>
      <Entry author="Justin Hammond - Justin@dynam.ac" date="24 May 2019" revision="3">Initial Metadata Import from Z-Wave Alliance Database - https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/1730/xml</Entry>
      <Entry author="Justin Hammond - Justin@dynam.ac" date="24 May 2019" revision="4">Updated Metadata Import from Z-Wave Alliance Database - https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/1731/xml</Entry>
      <Entry author="Jean-Francois Auger- Nechry@gmail.com" date="25 May 2019" revision="5">Apply PR #1546 from kaburke</Entry>
    </ChangeLog>
  </MetaData>
  <!-- Configuration Parameters -->
  <CommandClass id="112">
    <Value genre="config" index="4" label="Invert switch" max="1" min="0" size="1" type="list" value="0">
      <Help>Change the top of the switch to OFF and the bottom of the switch to ON if the switch was installed upside down.</Help>
      <Item label="No" value="0"/>
      <Item label="Yes" value="1"/>
    </Value>
    <Value genre="config" index="7" label="Remote level percent" max="99" min="1" type="short" units="%" value="99">
      <Help>Indicates how much each level dims/brightens as a portion of the whole range when set remotely.</Help>
    </Value>
    <Value genre="config" index="8" label="Remote duration per level" max="255" min="1" size="2" type="short" units="cs" value="22">
      <Help>Indicates the time duration of each level when set remotely.</Help>
    </Value>
    <Value genre="config" index="9" label="Local level percent" max="99" min="1" type="short" units="%" value="99">
      <Help>Indicates how much each level dims/brightens as a portion of the whole range when set locally.</Help>
    </Value>
    <Value genre="config" index="10" label="Local duration per level" max="22" min="1" size="2" type="short" units="cs" value="22">
      <Help>Indicates the time duration of each level when set locally.</Help>
    </Value>
  </CommandClass>
  <!-- Association Groups -->
  <CommandClass id="133">
    <Associations num_groups="1">
      <Group index="1" label="Lifeline" max_associations="5"/>
    </Associations>
  </CommandClass>
</Product>
