<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Product xmlns='http://code.google.com/p/open-zwave/'>
	<!-- Configuration Parameters -->
	<CommandClass id="112">
		<Value type="byte" index="0" genre="config" label="Unidentified Parameter" units="" min="0" max="255" value="5">
			<Help>
				Parameter #0 is undocumented: let us know if you know what it does!
				Attributes (type, units, min and max) are wild guesses, except default value.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" index="1" genre="config" label="On Time" units="minutes" min="0" max="255" value="20">
			<Help>
				On Time sets the number of minutes that the lights stay on when
				motion has not been detected.
				A value of 0 On Time is a special mode where the lights are
				constantly sent a command to turn them on whenever motion is
				detected. The device will NOT turn the lights off in this mode.
				Note that this mode will significantly shorten battery life.
				Recommended values:
				5 min for hallways.
				20 min for an office environment.
				60 min for a library or other room where someone may be sitting
				still for a long time.
				This may be inaccurate, but default for Homeseer HSM100 may actually be 3 minutes, instead of 20?				
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" index="2" genre="config" label="On Level" min="-1" max="99" value="99">
			<Help>
				OnLevel is the value sent by the Z-Wave BASIC_SET command to all Association Group 2 nodes when motion is detected. 
				A value of 0 will turn the lights off (not recommended).
				A value between 1 and 99 will set the dim level to between 1% and 99% (99% is full on).
				A value of -1 will turn the light on which depends on the device but most will set the dim level to the last dim setting.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" index="3" genre="config" label="Lite Minutes" min="0" max="255" value="5">
			<Help>
				LiteMinutes. A Luminance report is sent to the system controller every LiteMin minutes.
				A value of zero turns this mode off. Luminance values can still be obtained at any time by the home control application in this mode.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" index="4" genre="config" label="Temp Minutes" min="0" max="255" value="5">
			<Help>
				TempMinutes. A Temperature report is sent to the controller every TempMin minutes.
				A value of zero turns this mode off. Temperature values can still be obtained at any time by polling the status of the temperature sensor.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" index="5" genre="config" label="Temp Adj" min="-128" max="127" value="0">
			<Help>
				TempAdj. TempAdj is a twos-complement number that is used to adjust the temperature reading to make it more accurate. The value is in tenths of degree Fahrenheit. The temperature reading can be adjusted by +12.7F to -12.8F. A value of 1 will adjust the temperature reading by +0.1F. A value of -1 will adjust the temperature by -0.1F. A value of 123 will adjust the temperature by +12.3F.
			</Help>
		</Value>
	</CommandClass>
	<!-- Association Groups -->
	<CommandClass id="133">
		<Associations num_groups="2">
			<Group index="1" max_associations="1" label="Motion Notification" />
			<Group index="2" max_associations="4" label="Motion Control" auto="true"/>
		</Associations>
	</CommandClass>
</Product>
