<Product Revision="2" xmlns="https://github.com/OpenZWave/open-zwave">
  <MetaData>
    <MetaDataItem name="OzwInfoPage"></MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductPic">images/technisat/03009497.png</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="1000" name="ZWProductPage" type="0303">https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/3798/</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="WakeupDescription">TechniSat Dimmer-Switch is powered with mains voltage so it is always awake.</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ResetDescription">Use this procedure only when the network primary controller is missing or otherwise inoperable.
      1. Press and hold position T2 for more than 20 seconds.
      2. The LED will alternately flash red and green for 5 seconds after a successful reset.
</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="1000" name="Identifier" type="0303">0300/9497</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="Name">Dimmer</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="InclusionDescription">1. Install the TechniSat Dimmer.
      2. After checking the correct installation, re-enable electrical power at the main fuse or circuit breaker.
      3. Start the Z-Wave device add mode on your Z-Wave gateway, according to the gateway‘s manual.
      4. Press T1 3x within 1 second.
      5. The red status LED is on while the device is added to the Z-Wave network.
      6. The green LED is on for 5 seconds after successfully adding the device.
</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductManual">https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductManual/File?folder=&amp;filename=product_documents/3798/Manual_SMD01_Dimmer.pdf</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="1000" name="FrequencyName" type="0303">CEPT (Europe)</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ExclusionDescription">1. Start the Z-Wave device remove mode on your Z-Wave gateway, according to the gateway‘s manual.
      2. Press and hold position T1 for more than 10 seconds.
      3. The red status LED is on while the device is removed from the Z-Wave network.
      4. The green LED is on for 5 seconds after successfully removing the device.
</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="Description">Designed as a drop-in replacement for your single wall switch or dimmer from leading brand manufacturers, TechniSat's Dimmer integrates your wall switch into the Smart Home future.
       Featuring Z-Wave SmartStart and S2 security for easy installation and secure operation, yourdimmer can now be controlled from your Smart Home as well.
       ● Full manual operation
       ● can trigger central scenes via multiple button clicks
       ● Integrated 230 V auxiliary input for push button or toggle switch types, applicable in alternating switching and or intermediate switching circuits
       ● Short circuit and overload protection monitoring
</MetaDataItem>
    <ChangeLog>
      <Entry author="Technikte - technikte@mail.de" date="16 Aug 2020" revision="1">Initial file based on the work of Mathis Klooss for the Single-Switch and z-wavealliance.org information+local handbook</Entry>
      <Entry author="Andreas Krueger - ankrueg@gmx.de" date="03 Jan 2021" revision="2">Value type for "Parameter 2" and "Parameter 3" changed to "short" as parameter size is 2 bytes.</Entry>
    </ChangeLog>
  </MetaData>
  <!-- Configuration -->
  <CommandClass id="112">
    <Value type="list" genre="config" instance="1" index="1" label="Parameter 1" size="1" value="1">
      <Help>
        Enable/disable central scene notifications for 2x-5x button presses.
      </Help>
      <Item label="disable central scene" value="0" />
      <Item label="enable central scene" value="1" />
    </Value>
    <Value type="short" genre="config" instance="1" index="2" label="Parameter 2" value="3" min="0" max="8640">
      <Help>
        3 to 8640 - Interval of unsolicited reports in 10s increments, a value of 3 means 30 seconds (30 seconds - 1 day)
        0 - Disable unsolicited meter reports of current wattage.
      </Help>
    </Value>
    <Value type="short" genre="config" instance="1" index="3" label="Parameter 3" value="60" min="0" max="30240">
      <Help>
        Interval of active energy meter reports in minutes.
         - 10 to 30240 - Interval of active energy meter unsolicited reports in minutes (10 minutes - 3 weeks)
         - 0 - Disable unsolicited meter reports of active energy.
      </Help>
    </Value>
    <Value type="list" genre="config" instance="1" index="4" label="Parameter 4" size="1" value="0">
      <Help>
        Operations mode for push buttons controlling the output.
         - Normal Switch: In this mode the top button will turn the output on, while the bottom button will turn the output off.
         - Toogle Switch: In this mode any button press will toggle the output - when on it will be turned off, when off it will be turned on.
      </Help>
      <Item label="Normal Switch" value="0" />
      <Item label="Toogle Switch" value="1" />
    </Value>
    <Value type="list" genre="config" instance="1" index="5" label="Parameter 5" size="1" value="0">
      <Help>
        Configuration of switch type connected to extension input S.
         - External Normal Switch: Use this value if a toggle switch is connected to extension input S.
         - External Push Button: Use this value if a push button switch is connected to extension input S.
      </Help>
      <Item label="External Normal Switch" value="0" />
      <Item label="External Push Button" value="1" />
    </Value>
    <Value type="list" genre="config" instance="1" index="6" label="Parameter 6" size="1" value="1">
      <Help>
        Central Scene mapping of extension input S.
         - Central Scene 1: Multiple button presses (2x-5x) on extension input S will trigger events of central scene 1.
         - Central Scene 2: Multiple button presses (2x-5x) on extension input S will trigger events of central scene 2.
         - Central Scene 3: Multiple button presses (2x-5x) on extension input S will trigger events of central scene 3 - an additional central scene exclusive to extension input S.
      </Help>
      <Item label="Central Scene 1" value="1" />
      <Item label="Central Scene 2" value="2" />
      <Item label="Central Scene 3" value="3" />
    </Value>
    <Value type="list" genre="config" instance="1" index="7" label="Parameter 7" size="1" value="0">
      <Help>
        Select the dimming curve that should be used.
      </Help>
      <Item label="Dimming Curve 1" value="0" />
      <Item label="Dimming Curve 2" value="1" />
    </Value>
  </CommandClass>
  <!-- Association Groups -->
  <CommandClass id="133">
    <Associations num_groups="2">
      <Group index="1" label="Lifeline" max_associations="1"/>
      <Group index="2" label="Basic on/off" max_associations="10"/>
    </Associations>
  </CommandClass>
</Product>
