<Product Revision="3" xmlns="https://github.com/OpenZWave/open-zwave">
  <MetaData>
    <MetaDataItem name="OzwInfoPage">http://www.openzwave.com/device-database/013C:0010:0001</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductPic">images/philio/pan05.png</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="0010" name="ZWProductPage" type="0001">https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/1149/</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="0010" name="FrequencyName" type="0001">CEPT (Europe)</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ExclusionDescription">1.  Put your Z-Wave controller into exclusion mode by following the instructions provided by the controller manufacturer. 
2.  Pressing Include button of PAN05 three times within 2 seconds will enter inclusion mode. </MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="Description">This in-wall switch module is a transceiver which is a security enabled device which based on Z-Wave Plus technology, and it is fully compatible with any Z-Wave™ enabled network. Mini size design let the module can easily hide itself into the wall box and that will be good for the house decoration. Since PAN05 supports Security Command Class, it can learn with Secured controller. Its functionality and supported command classes is identical when included as a secure and non-secure device. 

There are many kind of application by using the module to switch Load On and Off, one main application is the light control. If connect the COM terminal directly to AC Line  terminal,  the  new  smart  relay  calibration  technology  can  reduce  the  inrush current caused by the load and let the module work perfectly with many kind of light like  incandescent,  fluorescent  and  LED  light.  This  module  can  also  connect  to alternative  power  supply  like  DC  12V  to  switch  on/off  12V  MR-16  light.

</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="InclusionDescription">1.  Put your Z-Wave controller into inclusion mode by following the instructions provided by the controller manufacturer. 
2.  Pressing Include button of PAN05 three times within 2 seconds will enter inclusion mode. 
</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ResetDescription">This procedure should only be used in the event that the primary controller is lost or otherwise inoperable.
1.  Pressing Include button of PAN05 three times within 2 seconds will enter inclusion mode. 
2.  Within 1 second, press Include button of PAN05 again for 5 seconds. 
3.  IDs are excluded. </MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="Name">In Wall Single relay (1 way) switch  module</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductManual">https://Products.Z-WaveAlliance.org/ProductManual/File?folder=&amp;filename=Manuals/1149/PAN05-1-2-3A manual-20140923.pdf</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="0010" name="Identifier" type="0001">PAN05-1A</MetaDataItem>
    <ChangeLog>
      <Entry author="Justin Hammond - Justin@dynam.ac" date="08 May 2019" revision="3">Initial Metadata Import from Z-Wave Alliance Database - https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/1149/xml</Entry>
    </ChangeLog>
  </MetaData>
  <!-- Configuration Parameters -->
  <CommandClass id="112">
    <Value genre="config" index="1" instance="1" label="Inputs S1 and S2 configuration" max="3" min="1" size="1" type="list" value="1">
      <Help>To match different kind of external switches, the inputs S1 and S2 can be set to either Edge Mode, Pulse Mode or Edge/Toggle Mode. Edge Mode: The Position of the external switch determines the switching state of the relay. After a wireless switching command it may be needed to operate the switch twice to return to the direct relation of switch position and relay state. Toggle Mode: Each ON-Position of the external switch will toggle the state of the relays. This mode is particularly suited for mono-stable switches. Edge/Toggle-Mode: Every change of the state of the external switch results in a change of the relay state. Default setting: Edge Mode</Help>
      <Item label="Edge Mode" value="1"/>
      <Item label="Pulse Mode" value="2"/>
      <Item label="Edge/Toggle Mode" value="3"/>
    </Value>
    <Value genre="config" index="2" instance="1" label="Switch state after cycling power" max="2" min="0" size="1" type="list" value="1">
      <Help>When the AC power returns, e.g. after a power failure, the relay states can be set to Off, On or to retain it's last state . Default setting: Retain last state</Help>
      <Item label="Switch Off" value="0"/>
      <Item label="Retain last state" value="1"/>
      <Item label="Switch On" value="2"/>
    </Value>
    <Value genre="config" index="3" instance="1" label="Manual On/Off mode" max="1" min="0" size="1" type="list" value="1">
      <Help>The On/Off function of S1,S2 and learn switch can be disabled or enabled by this parameter, default value is Enable. But the learning operation wont be affected. When manual On/Off function is disabled, the RF command can only switch On but not Off. This is useful function for keeping the device in switch on state</Help>
      <Item label="Disable manual On/Off" value="0"/>
      <Item label="Enable manual On/Off" value="1"/>
    </Value>
    <Value genre="config" index="4" instance="1" label="LED indication mode" max="3" min="1" size="1" type="list" value="1">
      <Help>Controls the light indicator in the device
               Switch State: When switch is on, LED is on. When switch is off, LED is off. (default)
               Night mode: When switch is on, LED is off. When switch is off, LED is on.
               One flash: When the device changes state, the LED illuminates for one second.
         </Help>
      <Item label="Switch state" value="1"/>
      <Item label="Night mode" value="2"/>
      <Item label="One flash" value="3"/>
    </Value>
    <Value genre="config" index="5" instance="1" label="Auto off" max="32767" min="0" type="short" value="0">
      <Help>After being switched on, the relays can be set to automatically switch off after the specified time. Available settings: 1-32767: time in seconds, 0: function disabled. Default setting: 0</Help>
    </Value>
    <Value genre="config" index="6" instance="1" label="Z-Wave Off command action" max="3" min="0" size="1" type="list" value="0">
      <Help>Action when a Z-Wave Off command is received. Default setting: Switch Off</Help>
      <Item label="Switch Off" value="0"/>
      <Item label="Ignore" value="1"/>
      <Item label="Toggle switch" value="2"/>
      <Item label="Switch On" value="3"/>
    </Value>
  </CommandClass>
  <CommandClass id="96">
    <Compatibility>
      <MapRootToEndpoint>true</MapRootToEndpoint>
    </Compatibility>
  </CommandClass>
  <!-- COMMAND_CLASS_ALARM does not respond to requests -->
  <CommandClass action="remove" id="113"/>
  <!-- Association Groups -->
  <CommandClass id="133">
    <Associations num_groups="1">
      <Group index="1" label=" Report ON/OFF status of Relay" max_associations="1"/>
    </Associations>
  </CommandClass>
</Product>
