<!-- Zipato: PH-PSG01 Smoke Sensor --><Product Revision="3" xmlns="https://github.com/OpenZWave/open-zwave">
  <MetaData>
    <MetaDataItem name="OzwInfoPage">http://www.openzwave.com/device-database/013C:001E:0002</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductPic">images/philio/phpsg01.png</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="001E" name="ZWProductPage" type="0002">https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/1167/</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="Name">Smoke Sensor</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="Description">The  Smoke  Sensor   PSG01   is   designed   to   give   early   warning   of developing fires by giving off the alarm sounds from its build-in alarm horn, based on Z-Wave™  technology.
It is a Z-Wave™ plus product, it supports the security, OTA... Those newest features of the  Z-Wave™  technology.  Z-Wave™ is a wireless communication protocol designed for home automation, specifically to remotely control   applications in residential and light commercial environments. The technology uses a low-power RF radio embedded or retrofitted into home electronics devices and systems, such as lighting, home access control, entertainment systems and household appliances.</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="InclusionDescription">1. Have Z-Wave™ Controller entered inclusion mode.
2. Pressing button three times within 1.5 seconds to enter the inclusion mode.
3. After add successful, the device will wake to receive the setting command from Z-Wave™ Controller about 20 seconds.</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ExclusionDescription">1. Have Z-Wave™  Controller entered exclusion mode.
2. Pressing button three times within 1.5 seconds to  enter the exclusion mode. Node ID has been removed.</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductManual">https://Products.Z-WaveAlliance.org/ProductManual/File?folder=&amp;filename=Manuals/1167/PSG01_Manual.pdf</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ResetDescription">Notice: Use this procedure only in the event that the primary controller is lost or otherwise inoperable.
1. Pressing button four times within 1.5 seconds and do not release the button in the 4 th  pressed, and the red LED will light ON.
2. After the red LED flash 9 times, release the button within 2 seconds.
3. IDs are removed and all settings will reset to factory default.</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="001E" name="Identifier" type="0002">PSG01</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="001E" name="FrequencyName" type="0002">CEPT (Europe)</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="WakeupDescription">After the device adding to the network, it will wake-up once per day in default. When it wake-up it will broadcast the “Wake Up Notification” message  to  the  network,  and  wake-up  10  seconds  for  receive  the setting commands. The wake-up interval minimum setting is 30 minutes, and maximum setting is 120 hours. And the interval step is 30 minutes. If the user want to wake-up the device immediately, please press the button once. The device will wake-up 10 seconds.</MetaDataItem>
    <ChangeLog>
      <Entry author="Justin Hammond - Justin@dynam.ac" date="08 May 2019" revision="3">Initial Metadata Import from Z-Wave Alliance Database - https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/1167/xml</Entry>
    </ChangeLog>
  </MetaData>
  <!-- Configuration Parameters -->
  <CommandClass id="112">
    <Value genre="config" index="7" label="Customer Function" max="127" min="0" type="byte" value="4">
      <Help>
                Customer function switch, using bit control.
                Bit0: Reserve.
                Bit1: Reserve.
                Bit2: Reserve => 1.
                Bit4: Notification Type (0: Notification Report, 1: Sensor Binary Report).
                Bit5: Reserve.
                Bit6: Reserve.
                Bit7: Reserve.
            </Help>
    </Value>
    <Value genre="config" index="10" instance="1" label="Auto Report Battery Time" max="127" min="1" type="byte" units="30 min" value="12">
      <Help>
                The interval time for auto report the battery level.
                30 minutes per tick and minimum time is 30 minutes, default tick is 12 (6 hours)
            </Help>
    </Value>
  </CommandClass>
  <!-- Basic set as report -->
  <CommandClass id="32">
    <Compatibility>
      <SetAsReport>true</SetAsReport>
    </Compatibility>
  </CommandClass>
  <!-- Association Groups -->
  <CommandClass id="133">
    <Associations num_groups="1">
      <Group index="1" label="Lifeline" max_associations="8"/>
    </Associations>
  </CommandClass>
</Product>
