<Product Revision="1" xmlns="https://github.com/OpenZWave/open-zwave">
  <MetaData>
    <MetaDataItem name="Name">10 Year Smoke Detector</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="Description">This products consists of a standard high-quality photo electric Smoke detector with a pluggable Z-Wave wireless interface module. The Smoke detector will also work as a stand alone product and is certified as '10 year Smoke Detector' The smoke chamber of the detector has a stainless steel reel with antistatic plastic chamber. A button allows on-device test of smoke chamber, electronics and battery. The device also offers a built-in self test and an electronic smoke chamber test to avoid the use of test aerosol. A low battery warning will last for 30 days but full function of the detector is guaranteed during this time. The Z-Wave module allows to report the smoke and low battery alarm wirelessly to a central controller.</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="OzwInfoPage">http://www.openzwave.com/device-database/0154:0004:000D</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductPage">https://www.popp.eu/products/sensors/10-jahres-rauchmelder-700342/</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductSupport">https://www.popp.eu/support/manuals/</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductPic">images/popp/009402.png</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductManual">https://www.popp.eu/005107en</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="WakeupDescription">A double click on the Z-Wave button wakes up the device></MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="InclusionDescription">Secure Inclusion: Push the button for 3 seconds, Unsecure Inclusion: Push the button for 1 seconds</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ExclusionDescription">Push the button for 1 second</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ResetDescription">To reset the device keep the button pushed for 10 seconds. After 5 seconds the led starts flashing and after another 5 seconds there is a short beep signaling the successful reset back to factory defaults. Use this procedure only when the network primary controller is missing or otherwise inoperable.</MetaDataItem>
    <ChangeLog>
      <Entry author="Márton Rubi - rubimart@airlink.hu" date="06 Jan 2020" revision="1">From the User Manual and the 009402.xml</Entry>
    </ChangeLog>
  </MetaData>
  <CommandClass id="112">
    <Value genre="config" index="3" instance="1" label="Value of On-Command" max="99" min="0" size="1" type="byte" value="99">
      <Help>This value is sent as BASIC Set to Association Group 3 when an Smoke Alarm occurs.</Help>
    </Value>
    <Value genre="config" index="4" instance="1" label="Value of Off-Command" max="99" min="0" size="1" type="byte" value="99">
      <Help>This value is sent as BASIC Set to Association Group 3 when an Smoke Alarm is cleared. </Help>
    </Value>
  </CommandClass>
  <!-- Association Groups -->
  <CommandClass id="133">
    <Associations num_groups="2">
      <Group index="1" label="Lifeline" max_associations="10"/>
      <Group index="2" label="Switching Command when Alarm" max_associations="10"/>
    </Associations>
  </CommandClass>
</Product>
