<!-- Configuration Parameters - per https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/1879 --><Product Revision="6" xmlns="https://github.com/OpenZWave/open-zwave">
  <MetaData>
    <MetaDataItem name="OzwInfoPage">http://www.openzwave.com/device-database/0063:3036:4952</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductPic">images/ge/14291-switch.png</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="3036" name="ZWProductPage" type="4952">https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/2501/</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ExclusionDescription">1. Follow the instructions for your Z-Wave certified controller to exclude a device from the Z-Wave network. 
2. Once the controller is ready to exclude your device, press and release the top button of the wireless smart switch (rocker) to exclude it from the network.</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="3036" name="Identifier" type="4952">14291/ZW4005</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="Description">Transform any home into a smart home with the GE Z-Wave In-Wall Smart Switch. The on/off switch replaces your current light switch, uses your existing wiring, and provides Z-Wave wireless and in-wall control of overhead lighting. The switch enables wireless control of on/off functions of direct wire incandescent, LED, xenon, halogen and fluorescent lighting. Providing ultimate flexibility, the GE Z-Wave Smart Lighting Control On/Off Switch allows you to operate the switch by itself or easily integrate the switch with two-way, three-way or four-way wiring configurations by adding the GE Add-On switch. Single pole wiring configuration turns the light or appliance on/off from one location. Three-way wiring configuration turns the light on/off from two separate locations. Four-way wiring configuration turns the light on/off from three separate locations. The GE Add-On Switch is required for Three-way or Four-way installations. The lighting control includes a blue LED indicator light to easily locate the switch in a dark room. Take control of your home lighting with GE Z-Wave Smart Lighting Controls!</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ResetDescription">1. Quickly press ON (Top) button 3 times then immediately press the OFF (Bottom) button 3 times. The LED will flash ON/OFF 5 times when completed successfully. 
2. Please use this reset procedure only when the primary controller is missing or inoperable. </MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="3036" name="FrequencyName" type="4952">U.S. / Canada / Mexico</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="Name">In-Wall Smart Switch </MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductManual">https://Products.Z-WaveAlliance.org/ProductManual/File?folder=&amp;filename=Manuals/2501/Binder1.pdf</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="InclusionDescription">1. Follow the instructions for your Z-Wave certified controller to include a device to the Z-Wave network.
2. Once the controller is ready to include your device, press and release the top or bottom of the wireless smart switch(rocker) to include it in the network.
3. Once your controller has confirmed that the device has been included, refresh the Z-Wave network to optimize performance.</MetaDataItem>
    <ChangeLog>
      <Entry author="Justin Hammond - Justin@dynam.ac" date="08 May 2019" revision="3">Initial Metadata Import from Z-Wave Alliance Database - https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/1438/xml</Entry>
      <Entry author="Justin Hammond - Justin@dynam.ac" date="24 May 2019" revision="4">Updated Metadata Import from Z-Wave Alliance Database - https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/1879/xml</Entry>
      <Entry author="Justin Hammond - Justin@dynam.ac" date="02 Jun 2019" revision="5">Updated Metadata Import from Z-Wave Alliance Database - https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/2501/xml</Entry>
      <Entry author="Brian France" date="23 Nov 2020" revision="6">Added COMMAND_CLASS_BASIC block to set Value type instead of Node Event for Basic Set, default double tap association auto=true</Entry>
    </ChangeLog>
  </MetaData>
  <CommandClass id="112">
    <Value genre="config" index="3" label="LED Light" max="2" min="0" size="1" type="list" value="0">
      <Help>Sets when the LED on the switch is lit.</Help>
      <Item label="LED on when light off" value="0"/>
      <Item label="LED on when light on" value="1"/>
      <Item label="LED always off" value="2"/>
    </Value>
    <Value genre="config" index="4" label="Invert Switch" max="1" min="0" size="1" type="list" value="0">
      <Help>Change the top of the switch to OFF and the bottom of the switch to ON, if the switch was installed upside down.</Help>
      <Item label="No" value="0"/>
      <Item label="Yes" value="1"/>
    </Value>
  </CommandClass>
  <!-- Association Groups -->
  <CommandClass id="133">
    <Associations num_groups="3">
      <Group index="1" label="Lifeline" max_associations="5"/>
      <Group index="2" label="Basic - Local Load" max_associations="5"/>
      <Group index="3" label="Basic - Double Tap" max_associations="5" auto="true" />
    </Associations>
  </CommandClass>
  <!-- COMMAND_CLASS_BASIC -->
  <CommandClass id="32">
    <Compatibility>
      <IgnoreMapping>true</IgnoreMapping>
      <SetAsReport>true</SetAsReport>
    </Compatibility>
  </CommandClass>
</Product>
