<Product Revision="2" xmlns="https://github.com/OpenZWave/open-zwave">
  <MetaData>
    <MetaDataItem name="OzwInfoPage">http://www.openzwave.com/device-database/0063:3135:4952</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductPic">images/ge/46201-switch.png</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="3135" name="ZWProductPage" type="4952">https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/3317/</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ExclusionDescription">1. Follow the instructions for your Z-Wave certified controller to exclude a device from the Z-Wave network. 
2. Once the controller is ready to exclude your device, press and release the top button of the wireless smart switch (rocker) to exclude it from the network.</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="3135" name="Identifier" type="4952">14291/46201/ZW4008</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="Description">In-Wall Smart Switch with QuickFit and SimpleWire enhancements. Revolutionary QuickFit design features a housing depth that is up to 20 percent smaller than the previous Z-Wave models. This reduced size coupled with the elimination of heat taps provides a better fit in older style boxes and multi-gang configurations. SimpleWire technology allows line and load to automatically be configured with auto-sensing line-load terminals. All of this is coupled with Z-Wave S2 and Smart Start allows for effortless installation while being safer than ever!</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ResetDescription">1. Quickly press ON (Top) button 3 times then immediately press the OFF (Bottom) button 3 times. The LED will flash ON/OFF 5 times when completed successfully. 
2. Please use this reset procedure only when the primary controller is missing or inoperable. </MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="3135" name="FrequencyName" type="4952">U.S. / Canada / Mexico</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="Name">In-Wall Smart Switch</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductManual">https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductManual/File?folder=&amp;filename=MarketCertificationFiles/3317/46201%20Binder.pdf</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="InclusionDescription">1. Follow the instructions for your Z-Wave certified controller to include a device to the Z-Wave network.
2. Once the controller is ready to include your device, press and release the top or bottom of the wireless smart switch(rocker) to include it in the network.
3. Once your controller has confirmed that the device has been included, refresh the Z-Wave network to optimize performance.</MetaDataItem>
    <ChangeLog>
      <Entry author="Caleb Mingle - caleb@mingle.cm" date="07 Sept 2019" revision="1">Initial Metadata Import from Z-Wave Alliance Database - https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/3317/xml</Entry>
      <Entry author="Brian France" date="23 Nov 2020" revision="2">Added COMMAND_CLASS_BASIC block to set Value type instead of Node Event for Basic Set, Added COMMAND_CLASS_ASSOCIATION block for double tap with double tap defauled to auto</Entry>
    </ChangeLog>
  </MetaData>
  <CommandClass id="112">
    <Value genre="config" index="3" label="LED Light" max="3" min="0" size="1" type="list" value="0">
      <Help>Sets when the LED on the switch is lit.</Help>
      <Item label="LED on when light off" value="0"/>
      <Item label="LED on when light on" value="1"/>
      <Item label="LED always off" value="2"/>
      <Item label="LED always on" value="3"/>
    </Value>
    <Value genre="config" index="19" label="Alternate Exclusion" max="1" min="0" size="1" type="list" value="0">
      <Help>Default - normal exclusion
        Active - perform a series of button presses to help eliminate accidental exclusion</Help>
      <Item label="Press any button" value="0"/>
      <Item label="Press two times ON, two times OFF" value="1"/>
    </Value>
  </CommandClass>
  <CommandClass id="133">
    <Associations num_groups="3">
      <Group index="1" label="Lifeline" max_associations="5"/>
      <Group index="2" label="Basic - Local Load" max_associations="5"/>
      <Group index="3" label="Basic - Double Tap" max_associations="5" auto="true"/>
    </Associations>
  </CommandClass>
  <!-- COMMAND_CLASS_BASIC -->
  <CommandClass id="32">
    <Compatibility>
      <IgnoreMapping>true</IgnoreMapping>
      <SetAsReport>true</SetAsReport>
    </Compatibility>
  </CommandClass>
</Product>
