<Product Revision="1" xmlns="https://github.com/OpenZWave/open-zwave">
  <MetaData>
    <MetaDataItem name="OzwInfoPage">http://www.openzwave.com/device-database/0330:D006:0200</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductPage">https://www.sunricher.com/z-wave-ac-in-wall-switch-sr-zv9101sac-hp-switch.html</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductPic">images/sunricher/srzv9101sachpswitch.png</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ResetDescription">Press and hold down the action button for over 10 seconds, the dimmer will be reset to factory defaults.

Note: Factory reset is not recommended for exclusion, please use this procedure only if the primary controller/gateway is missing or otherwise inoperable.</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="Description">The in-wall switch is a Z-Wave device that is used to switch ON/OFF the connected light and can be controlled
by other Z-Wave devices. The In-wall switch can be included and operated in any Z-Wave network with other ZWave certified devices from other manufacturers and/or other applications. All non-battery operated nodes
within the network will act as repeaters regardless of vendor to increase reliability of the network.</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="Name">Z-Wave AC In Wall Switch</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="InclusionDescription">1. Set primary controller/gateway into inclusion mode (Please refer to your primary controller’s manual on how to turn your controller into inclusion).
2. Power on the in-wall switch and set it into inclusion mode. There are two methods to set the in-wall switch into inclusion mode:
1)Repower on the switch, it will be set into inclusion mode automatically, and waiting to be included.
2)Triple press the action button on the switch, it will set the switch into inclusion mode.
The connected light will stay solid on for 3 seconds to indicate successful inclusion.</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ExclusionDescription">There are two exclusion methods:
Method 1: Exclusion from the primary controller/gateway as follows:
1. Set the primary controller/gateway into exclusion mode (Please refer to your primary controllers manual on how to set your controller into exclusion).
2. Triple press the action button, the switch will be set to exclusion mode, and waiting to be excluded, then the switch will be excluded from the network.
Method 2: Factory reset the switch will force it to be excluded from a network. (please refer to the part “Factory Reset” of this manual)
Note: Factory reset is not recommended for exclusion, please use this procedure only if the primary controller/gateway is missing or otherwise inoperable.</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductManual">https://www.sunricher.com/media/resources/manual/SR-ZV9101SAC-HP-Switch%20Instruction.pdf</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="D006" name="Identifier" type="0200">SR-ZV9101SAC-HP-Switch</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="D006" name="FrequencyName" type="0200">CEPT (Europe)</MetaDataItem>
    <ChangeLog>
      <Entry author="stevew817" date="13 Dec 2020" revision="1">Initial Configuration file</Entry>
    </ChangeLog>
  </MetaData>
  <!-- Configuration -->
  <CommandClass id="112">
    <Value genre="config" index="2" instance="1" label="Saving state before power failure" size="1" type="list" value="2">
      <Help>
              Saving state before power failure.
            Default Not saved.
        </Help>
      <Item label="State NOT saved at power failure, all outputs are set to OFF upon power restore" value="0"/>
      <Item label="State NOT saved at power failure, all outputs are set to ON upon power restore" value="1"/>
      <Item label="State saved at power failure, all outputs are set to previous state upon power restore" value="2"/>
    </Value>
    <Value genre="config" index="3" instance="1" label="Send the basic report" size="1" type="list" value="1">
      <Help>Enable/disable to send the basic report to the Lifeline when the load state changed.
              When value set as 1, re-power on the switch, it will send Basic report automatically.
		Default Enabled.
        </Help>
      <Item label="Disable" value="0"/>
      <Item label="Enable" value="1"/>
    </Value>
    <Value genre="config" index="7" instance="1" label="External switch to be added to and removed from a network" size="1" type="list" value="1">
      <Help>Enable/disable external switch to be added to and removed from a network.
              When enables this function, triple press the external switch within 1.5 seconds to be added to or removed from a net-work.
            Default Enabled.
        </Help>
      <Item label="Disable" value="0"/>
      <Item label="Enable" value="1"/>
    </Value>
  </CommandClass>
  <!-- Association Groups -->
  <CommandClass id="133">
    <Associations num_groups="1">
      <Group index="1" label="Lifeline" max_associations="1"/>
    </Associations>
  </CommandClass>
</Product>
