<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Product xmlns='http://code.google.com/p/open-zwave/'>
	<!-- Configuration Parameters -->
	<CommandClass id="112">
		<Value type="byte" index="0" genre="config" label="Unidentified Parameter" units="" min="0" max="255" value="5">
			<Help>
				Parameter #0 is undocumented: let us know if you know what it does!
				Attributes (type, units, min and max) are wild guesses, except default value.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" index="1" genre="config" label="Sensitivity" units="" min="0" max="255" value="200">
			<Help>
				Sensitivity sets the amount of motion required for the device to
				detect motion. A higher value makes it more sensitive and a
				lower value makes it less sensitive. Note that values above 200
				are not recommended when the device is battery operated.
				Recommended values:
				10 = Pet Immune.
				100 = Medium sensitivity for hallways.
				200(default) = Highly sensitive for rooms where people are sitting still.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" index="2" genre="config" label="On Time" units="minutes" min="0" max="255" value="20">
			<Help>
				On Time sets the number of minutes that the lights stay on when
				motion has not been detected.
				A value of 0 On Time is a special mode where the lights are
				constantly sent a command to turn them on whenever motion is
				detected. The device will NOT turn the lights off in this mode.
				Note that this mode will significantly shorten battery life.
				Recommended values:
				5 min for hallways.
				20 min for an office environment.
				60 min for a library or other room where someone may be sitting
				still for a long time.
				This may be inaccurate, but default for Homeseer HSM100 may actually be 3 minutes, instead of 20?				
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="list" index="3" genre="config" label="LED ON/OFF" units="" min="" max="" size="1" value="255">
			<Help>
				LED ON/OFF turns the LED on or off. A slight improvement in
				battery life is obtained by turning the LED off. Setting LED
				ON/OFF to zero will turn the LED off and 255 turns it on.
				Default is On (255).
			</Help>
			<Item label="Off" value="0"/>
			<Item label="On" value="255"/>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" index="4" genre="config" label="Light Threshold" units="%" min="0" max="100" value="100">
			<Help>
				Light Threshold is the percentage of light in the room above
				which the lights will not be turned on. Light Threshold is often
				used in room with a lot of natural daylight. Setting Light
				Threshold to a value of 50% will cause the device to not turn the
				lights on when the natural light in the room is already at the 50%
				value. This feature only prevents the lights from coming on when
				motion is first detected and the light level in the room is already
				above Light Threshold. It will not turn the lights off when the
				amount of natural light in the room increases. It will
				automatically turn on the lights in a room that has motion in it
				and that the amount of natural light has dropped below Light
				Threshold.
				A value of 100% turns off this feature (default).
				Recommended values:
				Usually a value between 40% and 60% will prevent the lights
				from coming on in a reasonably well light room and will turn
				them on as it is getting dark. Some experimentation is required
				with each room to determine the proper setting.				
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" index="5" genre="config" label="Stay Awake" units="" min="0" max="255" value="0">
			<Help>
				Setting Stay Awake to a non-zero value will cause the device to
				always be awake. NOTE: this mode should NOT be used when
				the device is battery powered! Batteries will only last a few days
				in this mode.
				Stay Awake is NOT set to the factory default (0) when the device
				is Excluded (reset) from the Z-Wave network.
				Setting Stay Awake to a non-zero value will cause the Z-Wave
				Listening Bit to be set. The device will become a routing node in
				the Z-Wave Mesh-Network when the Listening Bit is set.
				To properly have the device included in the routing tables, set
				Stay Awake to a non-zero value, then reset the device (Exclude
				from the network), then add it back to the network. The new
				routing information will be used now that the listening bit is set.
				Defaults to 0.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" index="6" genre="config" label="On Value" units="" min="0" max="255" value="255">
			<Help>
				On Value is the value sent by the Z-Wave BASIC_SET
				command when motion is detected.
				A value of 0 will turn the lights off (not recommended).
				A value between 1 and 100 will set the dim level to between 1%
				and 100%.
				A value of 255 will turn the light on (default).
				NB! According to the manual, the value should not be set between 101-254 (inclusive).
			</Help>
		</Value>
	</CommandClass>
	<!-- Association Groups -->
	<CommandClass id="96" mapping="endpoints" />
	<CommandClass id="133">
		<Associations num_groups="1">
			<Group index="1" max_associations="4" label="Motion" auto="true"/>
		</Associations>
	</CommandClass>
</Product>
