<Product Revision="2" xmlns="https://github.com/OpenZWave/open-zwave">
  <MetaData>
    <MetaDataItem name="OzwInfoPage">http://www.openzwave.com/device-database/0090:0446:0003</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductPic">images/kwikset/914c.png</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="0446" name="ZWProductPage" type="0003">https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/2268</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="0446" name="FrequencyName" type="0003">U.S. / Canada / Mexico</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="0446" name="Identifier" type="0003">914C</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductPage">https://www.kwikset.com/products/detail/kwikset-convert-smart-lock-conversion-kit-with-z-wave-technology</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="Description">Extend your smart home system to your current deadbolt, enabling your existing deadbolt to wirelessly communicate with your smart home or security system
Dramatically reduced, all-metal interior 
Works with existing select single cylinder deadbolts</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductSupport">http://www.kwikset.com/Customer-Support/Overview.aspx</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="Name">Convert Electronic Deadbolt</MetaDataItem>
    <ChangeLog>
      <Entry author="Jeff Sanicola - jeff.sanicola@outlook.com" date="20 Dec 2019" revision="1">Updated Metadata Import from Z-Wave Alliance Database - https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/2268/xml</Entry>
      <Entry author="steve28" date="14 Jun 2020" revision="2">Fixed index of alarm message to trigger lock status refresh</Entry>
    </ChangeLog>
    <MetaDataItem name="WakeupDescription">The electronic conversion kit remains asleep until an action occurs on the latch or a request is received from the RF side.
For the RF side, it will wake up every 1 second to check if there are any requests from your smart home controller.</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductManual">https://products.z-wavealliance.org/ProductManual/File?folder=&amp;filename=MarketCertificationFiles/2268/Install_Guide_914C_03_09_2017.pdf</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="InclusionDescription">Initiate the process to add the lock to your system at your smart home controller.
When prompted by your smart home system to add the lock, press button “A” on the lock interior one time. The red LED will illuminate when the lock enters Add Mode.
Please allow time for the controller to add the lock to your system.</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ExclusionDescription">Follow your smart home system’s instructions to remove the lock from the network. When prompted by the system, press button A” on the lock interior once.  The red LED will illuminate when the lock enters Remove mode. </MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ResetDescription">A factory reset will delete all user codes associated with the lock and will remove itself from your smart home system.
Please only perform a factory reset when the primary controller is missing or inoperable.

To perform a factory reset, please perform the following:  
1. Remove the battery pack
2. Press and HOLD the Program button while reinserting the battery pack.
3. Keep holding the button for 30 seconds until the lock beeps and the status LED flashes red.
4. Press the Program button once more.  The status LED will flash green and red several times.
5. After a few seconds, the lock will initiate the door handing process.</MetaDataItem>
  </MetaData>
  <!-- Configuration Parameters -->
  <CommandClass id="112">
    <Value genre="config" index="31" instance="1" label="Dipswitches state" max="255" min="0" read_only="true" type="byte">
      <Help>Bit mask field that returns the state of the user accessible Dipswitches on the door look.
			Bit 0 Lock LED Status (1: enable)
			Bit 1 Autolock (1: enable)
			Bit 2 Buzzer (1: enable)
			Bit 3 Handing Invert (1: enable)
      </Help>
    </Value>
    <Value genre="config" index="33" instance="1" label="MSB SKU part numbers" max="255" min="0" type="byte">
      <Help>The Configuration Parameter 33 and 34 are used to set the SKU part numbers to the Kwikset locks. 
			Is the first four most significant bytes (MSB). 
			Below describes how Configuration Parameter 33 and 34 are being used.
			* For a ZW Configuration Set, the DLM will first do a GET_SKU_ID to retrieve the full SKU from the lock, and the lock will respond with all 8 bytes. (If it not yet set, the DLM will consider that as all 0x30s.) 
			  The DLM changes only the appropriate 4 bytes in its local copy of the SKU, and it then sends the full 8 bytes down to the lock in a SET_SKU_ID.
			* For a ZW Configuration Get, the DLM will do a GET_SKU_ID down to the lock, to which the lock will respond with all 8 bytes. 
			  The DLM will return the requested 4 bytes via ZW. If the SKU is not set, it will return all 0x30s (ASCII 0s).
			</Help>
    </Value>
    <Value genre="config" index="34" instance="1" label="LSB SKU part numbers" max="255" min="0" type="byte">
      <Help>The Configuration Parameter 33 and 34 are used to set the SKU part numbers to the Kwikset locks. 
			Is the least four significant bytes (LSB). 			
      </Help>
    </Value>
    <Value genre="config" index="40" label="Reset To Factory Defaults" size="1" type="list" value="0" write_only="true">
      <Help>Reset to factory defaults</Help>
      <Item label="Perform Factory Reset" value="1"/>
      <Item label="Normal" value="0"/>
    </Value>
  </CommandClass>
  <CommandClass id="113">
    <!-- These Door Locks don't send a DoorLockReport when the
		Lock Status is Changed, but instead send a Alarm Message -
		So we trigger a Refresh of the DoorLock Command Class when
		we recieve a Alarm Message Instead -->
    <TriggerRefreshValue Genre="user" Index="6" Instance="1">
      <RefreshClassValue CommandClass="98" Index="1" Instance="1" RequestFlags="0"/>
    </TriggerRefreshValue>
  </CommandClass>
  <!-- Association Groups -->
  <CommandClass id="133">
    <Associations num_groups="1">
      <Group index="1" label="Lifeline" max_associations="5"/>
    </Associations>
  </CommandClass>
</Product>
